

Applicant for:

## **Developer Engineer (PHP or Android,iOS)**

Starboard Asia Co.,ltd. 15 September 2018

## **Phan Tuan Phong**

□ phongphan.dev@gmail.com

Main interests: Android, iOS

What skills, work projects or achievements make you a strong candidate for this position?

I've graduated from University Of Natural Sciences HCMC university and I have more years experience developing mobile applications from e commerce to mobile service for Singapore, Japan. I have more products had published on store, and special have product more than 3 million downloads. I strong knowledge in software programming and good at design UI/UX for mobile application. I believe with my experience, i can do good this position in your company.

# **Phan Tuan Phong**

SENIOR ANDROID DEVELOPER

### **Summary**

I've graduated from University Of Natural Sciences HCMC university and I have more 5 years experience developing mobile applications from e commerce to mobile service for Singapore, Japan. I have more products had published on store, and special have product near 3 million downloads on the world. I strong knowledge in software programming and good at design UI/UX for mobile application. Currently I am developing smart home cheap solutions for people. You can see demo here: <a href="http://thetreesoft.blogspot.com/2016/04/airswitch-bat-tat-thiet-bi-ien-trong.html">http://thetreesoft.blogspot.com/2016/04/airswitch-bat-tat-thiet-bi-ien-trong.html</a>



**Education** -

UNIVERSITY OF NATURAL SCIENCES HCMC

OCT 2008 - MAY 2013



**Certifications** -

CERTIFICATE ENGLISH B

2006



**Work Experience –** 

#### STARTUP, FREELANCER

**MAY 2013 - PRESENT** 

Senior Software Developer, founder

Freelancer: Make demo voice controller for car, TANCANG Parking solution.

Founder The Tree Team: provider tool apps on Android OS. With the mission to bring quality software to make your life simpler than ever. I had developed products and publish it onplaystore, research newtechnology, maketing to increased ownload.

My products: <a href="https://play.google.com/store/apps/developer?id=The+Tree+Team">https://play.google.com/store/apps/developer?id=The+Tree+Team</a>

JV-IT JSC APRIL 2016 - JULY 2018

Senior Software Developer

Developandroidapplicationsfor Japan. Inhere i writeapplicatonabout newspaper, Englishtesting, map,ibeacon,trackingsystem, magicwindow onsubway...

#### Projects:

- -Itsumo Navi: a Japan map similar Google Map but more complex (support underground and tracking don't use GPS)
- -Doutakanri: tracking location realtime of staff in building (use ibeacon technology, GPS...)
- -Madocon: magic window on Japan subway, it support touch, tracking location, tourguide
- -Seikyo Online: an online newspaper article view on mobile
- -Obunsya: English testing for student

**MAY 2014 - APRIL 2016** 

Senior Software Developer

**APPS CYCLONE** 

Developandroidapplicationsfor Singapore, Australiacustomers and products of company (games, chromecast technology). In here, iwrite code, research new technology and design UI/UX for app.



- (iii) October 26th, 1990
- Male
- 0977177754
- phongphan.dev@gmail.com
- Cu Chi district, Ho Chi Minh city
- i thetreesoft.blogspot.com

#### **SKILLS** -

Coding

Logical thinking and creative

Public Speaking

#### INTERESTS

- Soccer
- Music
- Reading books
- Science and Technology
- No smoking

#### Projects:

- -CYC Mover: help move office and house..
- -Clinic: registration for medical examination and treatment
- -Stray hat: look for lost objects in the school
- -ACE booking: booking for restaurant service
- -Honest bee: an e-commerce service that helps shopping at Singapore
- -Chromecast game: game about memory and can play it on chromecast TV



I was entered into the FbStart program and received \$80000 support for product development. FbStart is a global program designed to help startups build and grow their business of Facebook company. View more: <a href="https://developers.facebook.com/fbstart">https://developers.facebook.com/fbstart</a>

2016



#### **SOFT SKILLS**

- -Team work
- -Communication skill
- -Read, write by English language

#### **PROGRAMMING SKILLS**

- -C/C++, QT framework, Java
- -C#, ASP.NET
- -HTML, XML, JSON, Gson
- -SQL Lite, realm data base
- -Fire base
- -NDK
- -00PS

#### **SOFTWARE SKILLS**

- -Platforms: Windows, Linux, Smart phone (Symbian, android), Tablet, Google chrome cast
- -Others: Eclipse, NetBean, Visual Studio, Proteus, Codevison AVR, Unity, Cocos2dx, Photoshop
- -Version source control: GIT, SVN
- -Project manager: Trello, Redmine

#### **HARDWARE SKILLS**

- -Connection: I2C, UART
- -MCU: 8051, AVR, Arduino and more analog chip